KEIICHI KATSUNO

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER



PERSONAL SKILLS

- Emotional Awareness
- Individual Collaboration
- Relationship Development
- Research & Market Expansion

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails (Ruby)
- Javascript (ES6)
- HTML5 / CSS / Bootstrap
- SQLite & PostgreSQL
- GitHub

LANGUAGES

- Japanese (Native)
- English (Professional)
- Spanish (Elementary)

INTERESTS

- Non-Fiction (e.g. Anthropology / History / Business etc)
- Weight Training
- American Football
- Specialty Coffee

CONTACT

20 Newton Street Kensington, Victoria 3031 045 255 3653 keichi031605@gmail.com

 My Portfolio: https://keiichi031605.github.io/ keiichi-portfolio/

- Linkedin: keiichi katsuno

- GitHub: keiichi031605

PROFILE

Ruby on Rails Developer. Deep interest in SaaS and passionate about business improvement that has a real influence on people's life.

For the past 6 years, I've experienced Marketing and Relationship Development in Japan, and Production Management in The UK and Colombia. I'm especially competent in **Teamwork**, and proud of my **Emotional Awareness** for **Solving the Problems** as well as **Meeting the Needs**.

I place a high value on respect to people and learning independently in my life.

EXPERIENCE

OUALITY ASSURANCE SPECIALIST

InverCafé Ltda., Chinchiná, Colombia | Sep 2019 - Dec 2019 (Internship)

Quality Control of Harvested Green Coffee Products

- Developed: "Deep Industrial Knowledge" and "Marketing"

PRODUCTION MANAGER

The Roasting Shed Co., London, The UK | July 2018 - Sep 2019 (Full-time)

Production Development of High-Quality Coffee Products

- Developed: "Production Analysis & Development and "Marketing"

RELATIONSHIP MANAGER

Yuasa Trading Co., Japan | Apr 2013 - July 2017 (Full-time)

Business Partnership Development and Account & Order Management Focused on solving the problems for partners, therefore, achieved doubling my area sales targets within a 12-month period.

- Developed: "Sales & Marketing", "Project Management" and "Negotiation",

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION, SPORTS MANAGEMENT

Kinki University, Osaka, Japan | Apr 2009 - Mar 2013

Outside of study, engaged in American Football club, learning Organisational Theory & Team Management and Logical & Critical Thinking for organisational success.

PROJECT

"WHATSPOT"(SOCIAL NETWORKING SERVICE)

- The mobile app that you can share any places or recommendations with your friends so that you get more trusted information for your weekend!

URL: https://www.whatsthespot.com